watchmencomicmovie.com 2016-05-09

# Privacy Policy - WatchmenComicMovie.com

## 

### Statement

This Privacy Policy has been created by the operator of the WatchmenComicMovie.com Web site, in an effort to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy on our site. We do not collect any Personal Identifiable Information (PII) from people who browse our website.

### Email Addresses

Some features and services of WatchmenComicMovie.com require individuals to submit their email adddress. Under no circumstances will WatchmenComicMovie.com distribute or sell any obtained email addresses to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. 

### External Links

WatchmenComicMovie.com contains links to other sites which are not owned or operated by WatchmenComicMovie.com and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy and terms of use policies of each respective linked site individually before offering any of your personal information.

### Affiliate Programs

WatchmenComicMovie.com is currently participating in a number of affiliate programs who may collect information in order to process orders you place with them and/or to provide other services they offer. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy and terms of use policies of each respective affiliate before offering any of your personal information.

### About Children

WatchmenComicMovie.com is not directed to children under 13. Children under 13 MUST not submit personal information to WatchmenComicMovie.com and WatchmenComicMovie.com will not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

### Aggregated Information

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Any questions regarding privacy issues can be addressed to [hurm@WatchmenComicMovie.com](mailto:hurm@WatchmenComicMovie.com)
